Take it easy.
Mr. Attorney.
Can you hear me, Mr. Attorney?
Attorney Byeon!
Yeah, what is it?
They're using a lot of ammo up here.
Do they expect me to get hit and die?
No, Sang-ung.
They're merely trying
to restrict your liquidity.
Well, I'm used to being broke by now.
I'm almost there.
Just hold on a little longer. Okay.
When you neutralize the henchmen,
come into the branch manager's office.
MANAGER'S OFFICE
Through there, we can get
straight into the secret vault.
Once everything's ready,
I'll lower you down.
Seriously?
Hey. Bun-mi? Help, please!
Give me a second.
GIMHAE SAVINGS BANK
You either get Sang-ung
and bring him to me or die trying.
Yes, ma'am!
-I think I'm gonna puke.
-Hey.
You took your sweet time.
What? Wish I'd taken longer.
-First, find Kang Sang-ung.
-They're here.
We'll get the Mundane Vanguard
to fight Jo Anna's crew.
They'll be too tied up with each other
to chase after us.
And that way we'll be alone,
in the secret vault.
Mr. Attorney, do you copy?
We're heading to the office, all right?
It's not safe.
Attorney Byeon. Please respond.
There's no signal.
We better hurry.
We have to get down there fast.
Attorney Byeon?
Byeon, can you hear me?
Attorney Byeon, are you okay?
You never cease to amaze. Very impressive.
No matter which way you look at it,
your superpower is the greatest.
The greatest,
as long as you have enough money.
I'll shut you up with what I have here.
Here's a fun drug
we'll be releasing when it's ready.
Hey.
What are you getting out of all this?
Why go this far?
Well, money, of course.
When I finally take control
of your superpower,
I'll need as much money as I can get.
REPLENISH YOUR CALORIES!
That's all you got?
How anticlimactic.
What do you say, old-timer?
Should we call it quits?
Not a chance.
Min-suk has something fun to tell me.
I plan on hearing it.
Wrong way!
Is it last call yet?
Attorney Byeon!
Bun-mi!
Hey, can you hear me?
Attorney Byeon, can you hear me?
What a horrible smell.
I couldn't see it yet,
but I knew what it was.
It was an oddly familiar stench.
Like something I'd always dreamed about
but could never touch.
And that horrible smell is…
money.
What's so funny?
You know we're about to die, right?
GIMHAE BANK
UNDERGROUND VAULT
What do you think
is on the other side of that wall?
Sewer line?
You might think so from the rotten smell,
but that's not it.
What are you saying?
According to the blueprints,
this room is supposed to be 17 meters long
and 11 meters wide.
Don't you agree
there's some space missing?
It's true what they say.
Money really does give you confidence.
Still here?
Look who it is.
Huh.
Grandpa's alive.
I told you not to call me that.
So that's where he stashed it.
Your old man's hiding
one hell of a piggy bank.
Bun-mi, help Byeon outside.
Now that we're finally face-to-face,
I wanna say goodbye to our friend here.
What a relief. Let's go, Bun-mi.
I always knew money could fix my problems.
But this is a whole other level.
That's quite the power you have.
It's worth every last cent.
But what good is strength if you're blind?
I see everything.
Now say goodbye.
Can you take my best shot?
Huh?
What?
What the hell's going on?
This feels like waking up
after getting blackout drunk.
I can't seem to use my superpowers.
What the…
Don't worry. We're not taking you away.
Sit tight.
What the hell is he doing?
Nothing good.
Get out.
I'm sure you'll behave
now that your superpowers are gone.
Sorry?
-Get out of the car already.
-Hold on, wait! Hear me out.
Jo Nathan.
He's selling drugs that give superpowers.
I'll look into it.
You won't just look into it.
Go lock up that psycho.
Didn't I tell you
your actions could end up
hurting innocent people?
So you're saying this is my fault.
I mean, what do you expect me to do?
Just sit back and do nothing
while innocent people are getting hurt?
You think this is the first time
the world's been in danger?
Listen, kid, there hasn't been
a single instant when it hasn't.
There have always been thugs
like the Mundane Vanguard,
putting new drugs on the streets.
This fight started
before either of us were born,
and it'll keep going
long after we're dead.
There are more ways to fight back
than you think.
And a lot more people doing the fighting.
-Now get out of here.
-Please listen to me.
Come on, let's go! I'm getting hungry.
GIMHAE SAVINGS BANK
Get these ampoules into storage.
Yes, ma'am.
-And Lee Su-eun?
-I'm afraid she's still missing.
I want her captured right away.
Wow.
What are you doing down here?
Drop your guns.
Damn, it's hot under these.
Thanks to my son-in-law,
I finally get to see inside this place.
Who the hell are you, lady?
You must be Jo Won-do's daughter.
You're the spitting image of your father.
I don't agree.
Don't try anything stupid now.
Just stay nice and still.
I have no business here with you.
You went on a rampage,
fighting with someone else's money,
then passed out.
And when you regained consciousness,
your powers were gone, is that right?
Yeah.
You're maxed out, son.
I never get a straight answer
from this guy.
Am I some kind of credit card now?
What?
I'm saying you don't have the capacity
to handle your superpowers.
Kang Sang-ung, stay with me, okay?
Don't use other people's money.
It's one of the first things I told you.
Hang on. You… you gotta be…
When you said
not to use other people's money,
it seemed like you were giving
financial advice, not a steadfast rule.
If my powers are gone,
when do they return?
Who knows?
It's just like with anything else in life.
You can't let yourself get greedy.
Whether it's money, food, or alcohol.
The second you try to go
beyond your limits, you land in trouble.
The game is rigged.
This was never a fair fight to begin with.
If I have to use my own money,
and they're really fucking strong,
then I never stood a chance at all!
You could've passed this thing down
with some cash if you knew how it worked!
Listen, son.
This isn't about the money.
What do you mean?
Of course that's what it's about!
Only a moron could think otherwise.
What if your power has disappeared?
I…
You would let them win?
You'd let the Vanguard take your friends
all because you lost a lousy superpower?
You were willing to do
what most people wouldn't.
They wouldn't have used
their mother's gift
to save a bus of complete strangers.
The superpower wasn't
what saved those people.
It wasn't the cash either.
It was you.
Take some time to think about it.
You might find out,
the money isn't what gives you strength.
When you're in the fight…
…when you're protecting others…
there comes a moment of realization.
You realize
the money isn't that important.
You figure that out,
and you'll have your powers back
in no time.
THE MUNDANE VANGUARD
Shit.
The extent of that loser's superpowers
proved more than you could handle.
Having to live with your failure
is a punishment
that is far worse than death.
It's funny how pride works.
If you lose it, you lose everything.
Chairman.
JO ANNA
What is it now?
There are two things in this world
no one has ever been able
to keep me from getting my hands on.
BORROWER: JO SIN-IL
LENDER: PARK HYEONG-DO
The cash owed on a debt,
and the truth.
Sorry to let you down,
but I don't owe any debt.
That's not what
the ledger I'm holding says.
It's taken me a long time
to uncover your dirty little secret.
Your empire may have taken
a century to build…
but it can all come crashing down
in the blink of an eye.
You should know
I'm not as forgiving as my father was.
I suggest you cough up the cash you owe,
or your health could suffer.
Your phone, little girl.
You're gonna regret this.
Oh, really?
I'd watch my mouth
before you find out what regret is.
I'll keep this money safe.
You can tell your father that.
Take it away.
Yes, ma'am!
Having superpowers is a major pain.
But having them taken away
right when you're starting
to get the hang of them,
somehow, that's even worse.
Min-suk?
Hey, Min-suk!
Hey, Min…
Min-suk!
Oh shit.
-Uh, hello--
-I was touched by what you said earlier.
Where is Min-suk?
I'm here, Sang-ung. I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Hey, Min-suk.
Are you all right?
Uh, just hold on a little longer.
I'll be right there.
Why do you keep making things
more difficult?
Listen, let's figure this out.
You already know what I want.
Fine, then, I'll come to you.
Just leave Min-suk out--
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Hey, you motherfucker!
I said I'd come. I'm coming right now!
I decide when.
You just wait quietly.
Shit. Come on.
The person
you are trying to reach is unavailable…
You really think you're gonna win,
don't you?
You don't have what it takes
to beat Kang Sang-ung.
What makes you so sure?
Because Sang-ung…
is terrible at calculations.
In the end, he always chooses
to do what he thinks is right,
no matter how impossible
or how much he'll get hurt.
Ah, I see.
So that's why
that little loser is always broke.
No. Sang-ung was broke to begin with.
Why would you choose
a pushover like that guy?
He thinks he's a saint.
Yeah, but you've got it wrong.
That pushover is the one
who is putting up with me.
And I should warn you
that he's not a pushover for anyone else.
How touching.
Damn right, it's touching. I married him!
From where I sit,
it feels like you're trying
to take my husband away from me.
You ruined our dinner with the in-laws.
Now, we can't even have our wedding!
Just you wait and see.
You're gonna lose.
We'll see who makes it out of this.
Nobody move!
Jo Nathan. He's selling drugs
that give superpowers.
I'll look into it.
You won't just look into it.
Go lock up that psycho.
Why'd we go all the way out to Gimhae
to let him go first chance we get?
What's really going on here?
Kang Sang-ung. Why isn't he under arrest?
'Cause he hadn't committed a crime.
And since when did we start letting people
who break into safes go?
Look, guys.
There's one thing more valuable
than cash in this world.
Know what it is?
What?
It's time.
We never have enough of it,
and you couldn't buy even it if you tried.
You look great.
Don't be late next time.
Min-suk, where is she?
We'll get to that.
You need to pass a test first.
What kind of test?
I heard in the safe you passed out.
If it's true you lost your power,
then I think it's best
if everybody moves on.
That's when it hit me.
If I don't have my superpowers,
it means I'm completely useless to them.
If you take me down,
I'll take you to your girl.
But if you're impotent…
you and your little girly,
your days are numbered.
I'm sorry to say,
there's something fun
that Min-suk wanted to share.
So I think I'll stay above ground.
Min-suk.
Where is she?
Are you okay?
What happened to seeing everything?
Where is Min-suk?
Tell me where you're holding her.
You really have lost your powers.
It looks like both of you are dead.
My fight isn't with you.
Just tell me.
Min-suk.
Where is she?
You'll see her in hell.
One more step, you'll be Swiss cheese.
DIVORCE ATTORNEY BYEON HO-IN
BEOMHA LOGISTICS
Here it is.
FIRST FLOOR
The Mundane Vanguard has thugs
watching every entrance into the building.
HORIZONTAL CROSS SECTION
You can bet they're watching Min-suk too.
Going in now would be a suicide mission.
You would accomplish nothing,
and we will all be dead!
It'd be a long shot,
even with your powers.
When we first met,
you asked why I helped those people.
The bus accident.
Remember?
I did it because I had to.
There was no other choice.
With superpowers or without,
I'd still try.
Using belief alone
won't get you out alive.
Listen to my warnings.
I ran all the calculations, Sang-ung!
I'm terrible at calculations.
BEOMHA LOGISTICS
I think I understand
what my dad was trying to say.
My strength
doesn't come from money.
It comes from fighting
to protect something
that's more important than money.
That's true strength.
I'm on my way, Min-suk.
I promise I won't be late this time.
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine
Give me all the cash
I feel the fire now
Try to punch you, smash
Devil is into your mind
I am cynical, but I feel powerful
I can crush you now
Time is done you better run
Let me whisper to your mind
You will feel the burn
Supernatural
I got the power on my mind
I can give you all the pain
Till the break of dawn
I can fly up the sky
Every day and night
Drop it on the floor
Better listen now
You got nothing
And I know that this is over now
Chasing you around
Round merry-go-round
Boo, I got you
You will never see the light
Let me whisper to your mind
You will feel the burn
Supernatural
I got the power on my mind
I can give you all the pain
Till the break of dawn
I can fly up the sky
Every day and night
Burn the lonely eyes
Crucify your lies
Now you cry
You better run
Run it speed of light
You better run, run it till you fight
Pain through your heart
Pain through your soul
It's time
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine
No one else can find you now
Only devils on your side
You will see the darkest night
-I can fly
-Fly
Supernatural
I got the power
Devils in the night
-Try to fight
-Fight
Nothing can be stopped
Follow you tonight
This is all my life
Power's mine